[MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, so this isn't matching up with this.
I'm not sure which one's right.
Can you just hunt down the original part?
- Yes, me too.
All right.
Hey, Kev, what were you saying before about the paperwork?
Me doin' now.
Go. Stop worry.
Kevin, do you feel okay?
I feel good. Body strong. Sleep big last night.
Yeah, I think we should get him to the hospital.
Yeah, alright Kev, why don't you come with us?
No, no, he's fine. He's always been like that.
No, he hasn't.
I mean, he's gotten worse over the years.
He's making a statement. It's an ironic comment on our expectations of him.
A funhouse image of our model.
You keep think that.
Me mechanic not speak English, but he know what me mean when me say car no go and we best friends.
So me think why waste time say lot word
when few word do trick.
- Kevin, I appreciate what you're trying to do.
- Thank.
Here we have a word code the same way we have a dress code and what we're talking about is
Basically the speech equivalent
to just wearing underpants.
Sometimes words you know need use,
but need need for.
- But save time, more success.
- Does it save time though?
'Cause we've been here for about an hour.
- No me fault.
- Kevin?
At most you're saving a microscopic amount of time.
Many small time make big time.
And what are you going to do with all this time?
See you.
world.
Kevin, you can't possibly save enough time to see the world.
Kevin, are you saying "see the world" or "sea world"?
Sea world.
Oceans.
Fish, jump, China.
- No, see, right there, that's the problem with your method
'cause I still don't know if you're saying see world
or see the world and it's taken a lot of time.
Time to explain it.
Fine, fine. I'll talk normally.
When me, President, they see.
They see.